[
    {
        "question": "Boy: Shall we go out to the movie tonight?<br>Girl: No, we- _____finish our homework first. It has to be in tomorrow.",
        "options": [" a. might ", " b. would ", " c. could ", " d. should "],
        "answer": " d. should "
    },
    {
        "question": "Boy: What have you done to your leg?<br>Girl: Oh, I fell over yesterday and it ____hurts now.",
        "options": [" a. so ", " b. very ", " c. quite ", " d. really "],
        "answer": " d. really "
    },
    {
        "question": "Woman: _____did you get home last night?<br>Man: I got a taxi.",
        "options": [" a. How ", " b. When ", " c. What ", " d. Where "],
        "answer": " a. How "
    },
    {
        "question": "Woman: I can't afford to go away on holiday this year.<br>Man: What____ instead?\nWoman: I'm not quite sure yet.",
        "options": [" a. do you do ", " b. will you do ", " c. have you do ", " d. were you doing "],
        "answer": " b. will you do "
    },
    {
        "question": "Man: Does it cost____ to fly from London to Edinburgh?<br>Woman: I think it's cheaper if you book on the Internet.",
        "options": [" a. many ", " b. much ", " c. a few ", " d. a lot of "],
        "answer": " b. much "
    },
    {
        "question": "Boy: Do you like playing this computer game?<br>Girl: No. _____ is boring. Shall we choose something else to play?",
        "options": [" a. they're ", " b. it's ", " c. we're ", " d. I'm "],
        "answer": " b. it's "
    },
    {
        "question": "Woman: How many children_____ you got?<br>Man: Three. Two girls and a boy.",
        "options": [" a. do have ", " b. did ", " c. are ", " d. have "],
        "answer": " d. have "
    },
    {
        "question": "Man: Do you want to come with me to the supermarket?<br>Woman: No, thanks. I don't need_____",
        "options": [" a. it ", " b. something ", " c. one ", " d. anything "],
        "answer": " d. anything "
    },
    {
        "question": "Woman: Can I borrow a pen?<br>Man: Sorry, I _____ have one.",
        "options": [" a. didn't ", " b. won't ", " c. haven't got ", " d. don't "],
        "answer": " d. don't "
    },
        {
            "question": "Girl: Could I_____ your pen for a minute?<br>Boy: Yeah, sure!",
            "options": [" a. borrow ", " b. borrowed ", " c. lend ", " d. lent "],
            "answer": " a. borrow "
        },
        {
            "question": "Boy: Do you eat brown bread?<br>Girl: Not really. I_____ white better.",
            "options": [" a. like ", " b. want ", " c. prefer ", " d. eat "],
            "answer": " c. prefer "
        },
        {
            "question": "Man: _____ wrong?<br>Woman: I don't feel very well.",
            "options": [" a. How's ", " b. What's ", " c. Are you ", " d. What's matter "],
            "answer": " d. What's matter "
        },
        {
            "question": "Woman: I always travel by bus.<br>Man: Why?\nWoman: Because it's_____ than the train.",
            "options": [" a. much cheaper ", " b. as cheap ", " c. more cheap ", " d. cheap "],
            "answer": " a. much cheaper "
        },
        {
            "question": "Man: Is Anna here today?<br>Woman: No, _____ at home on Tuesdays.",
            "options": [" a. she is working ", " b. she would work ", " c. she works ", " d. she work "],
            "answer": " c. she works "
        },
        {
            "question": "Woman: _____ do you do?<br>Man: I'm a chef in a French restaurant.",
            "options": [" a. How ", " b. Where ", " c. What ", " d. Whose "],
            "answer": " c. What "
        },
        {
            "question": "Girl: Is Sam_____ than you now?<br>Boy: Yes. He's grown a lot recently.",
            "options": [" a. taller ", " b. the tallest ", " c. more taller ", " d. tall "],
            "answer": " a. taller "
        },
        {
            "question": "Woman: Where did you get that book?<br>Man: Peter gave it to_____ yesterday.",
            "options": [" a. me ", " b. my ", " c. mine ", " d. myself "],
            "answer": " a. me "
        },
        {
            "question": "Boy: When_____ George start learning Spanish?<br>Girl: About two years ago, I think.",
            "options": [" a. did ", " b. will ", " c. was ", " d. does "],
            "answer": " a. did "
        },
        {
            "question": "Woman: Would you like another coffee?<br>Man: No thanks, I've had_____.",
            "options": [" a. any ", " b. some ", " c. much ", " d. enough "],
            "answer": " d. enough "
        },
        
          {
                "question": "Man: The music was fantastic, wasn't it?<br>Woman: Yes, it was the best concert I've been_____ to.",
                "options": [" a. never ", " b. ever ", " c. just ", " d. already "],
                "answer": " b. ever "
            },
            {
                "question": "Girl: What are your plans for the weekend?<br>Boy: _____ to the cinema with Kirsty.",
                "options": [" a. go ", " b. went ", " c. will going ", " d. am going "],
                "answer": " d. am going "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: How long have you been in Australia?<br>Woman: Two months.\nMan: And do you_____ it in Sydney?",
                "options": [" a. like ", " b. live ", " c. find ", " d. want "],
                "answer": " a. like "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: I always look forward to the summer holidays.<br>Man: So _____I.",
                "options": [" a. do ", " b. am ", " c. can ", " d. have "],
                "answer": " a. do "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: I'm going to the mountains at the weekend, but I haven't got any climbing boots.<br>Man: Oh, do you want to borrow_____?",
                "options": [" a. my ", " b. me ", " c. mine ", " d. mines "],
                "answer": " a. my "
            },
            {
                "question": "Waiter: Who ordered the soft drink?\nMan: I did.<br>Waiter: _____. Enjoy!",
                "options": [" a. Right ", " b. Who is it? ", " c. Here you are ", " d. There you are. "],
                "answer": " c. Here you are "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: You look a bit stressed. What's the matter?<br>Man: I'm worried _____my job interview next week.",
                "options": [" a. to ", " b. for ", " c. of ", " d. about "],
                "answer": " d. about "
            },
            {
                "question": "Woman: How far is_____ to the bus stop?<br>Man: Just a couple of blocks away.",
                "options": [" a. it ", " b. that ", " c. this ", " d. there "],
                "answer": " c. this "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: What did you think of Paul's girlfriend?<br>Woman: I thought she was______ nice, but she talks all the time.",
                "options": [" a. much ", " b. quite ", " c. some ", " d. enough "],
                "answer": " b. quite "
            },
            {
                "question": "Man: These two coats look the same. Which one is yours?<br>Woman: I think mine's the one_____ the right.",
                "options": [" a. to ", " b. in ", " c. for ", " d. on "],
                "answer": " b. in "
            },
            {
                "question": "Girl: How often do you play football?<br>Boy: Actually, I _____ play football.",
                "options": [" a. often ", " b. never ", " c. always ", " d. usually "],
                "answer": " b. never "
            }
            
        ]
        
    
